Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Football Audiovisual Materials
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (11 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 69)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (12 of 18) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 69)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (13 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 69)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (14 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2) (copy), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (15 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (16 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2) (copy), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (17 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Punt, Kick-Off Return, PAT/FG] (1), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (18 of 18) [labeled on cassette as Punt, Kick-Off Return, PAT/FG] (2), 9 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (1 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (2 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Kent State (3 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (4 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (5 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Kent State (6 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (7 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Original), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (8 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (9 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Original), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (10 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (11 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (12 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Kent State (1 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (2 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (3 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (4 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (5 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (6 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2) (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (7 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (8 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2) (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (9 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (10 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (11 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (12 of 19) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (13 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (14 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2) (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (15 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (16 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2) (copy), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (17 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Kicking] (1), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (18 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Kicking] (2), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Kent State (19 of 19) [labeled on cassette as Kicking] (3), 30 Sept. 1989 (Carton 70)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 62)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 63)
  16mm film; Approximate runtime: 2 minutes, 30 seconds; color; no sound
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 10) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 10) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Maryland (10 of 10) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2) (copy), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2) (copy), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, End Zone-Tight], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (6 of 13) [labeled on canister as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (7 of 13) [labeled on canister as Defense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (8 of 13) [labeled on canister as Defense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (9 of 13) [labeled on canister as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (10 of 13) [labeled on canister as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (11 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking Master], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (12 of 13) [labeled on canister as Punt, Kickoff return, PAT/FG], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Maryland (13 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kickoff, Punt return/A team], 2 Sept. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (1 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (2 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (3 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (4 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (5 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (6 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (7 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (8 of 11) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (9 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (10 of 11) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (11 of 11) [labeled on canister as Kicking], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (1 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (2 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (3 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (4 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (5 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2) (copy), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (6 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (7 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2) (copy), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (8 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (9 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (10 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (11 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 71)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (12 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (13 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kicking Master], 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (14 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kicks] (1), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (15 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kickoff, Punt Return, PAT/FG block] (2), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. Middle Tennessee State University (16 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kickoff, Punt Return, PAT/FG] (3), 7 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (11 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (12 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 63)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (1 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (2 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (3 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (4 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (5 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (6 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (7 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (8 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (9 of 12) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (10 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (11 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. South Carolina (12 of 12) [labeled on cassette as Kickoff, Punt Return, PAT/FG block], 28 Oct. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (11 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (12 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #1), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (13 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Tight], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (5 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2) (copy), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (6 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (7 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2) (copy), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 72)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (8 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (9 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Tight], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (10 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (11 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
  Beta SP cassette; Approximate runtime: 30 minute; color; sound
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (12 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (13 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (14 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kicking], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (15 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kick-off, Punt Return, PAT/FG block], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (16 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Punt, Kick-off return, PAT/FG], 23 Sept. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 13) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (9 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (10 of 13) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (11 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (12 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #1), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (13 of 13) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (5 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (1 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (6 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (7 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (2 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (8 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (9 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (10 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (1 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (11 of 16) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (2 of 2), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (12 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (13 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (14 of 16) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (15 of 16) [labeled on cassette as End Zone Kicking Master], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 73)
- NC State vs. Virginia (16 of 16) [labeled on cassette as End Zone, Kick-Off, Punt Return, PAT-FG block], 4 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (1 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Original), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (2 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (3 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Offense] (Print #2), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (4 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Original), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 64)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (5 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 108)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (6 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Offense] (Print #2), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (7 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (8 of 12) [labeled on canister as 1st half Defense] (Print #2), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (9 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (10 of 12) [labeled on canister as 2nd half Defense] (Print #2), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (11 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Original), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (12 of 12) [labeled on canister as Kicking] (Print #1), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 65)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (1 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (2 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (3 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Offense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (4 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (5 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Offense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (6 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (7 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 1st half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (8 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (9 of 15) [labeled on cassette as 2nd half Defense, Sideline-Wide] (copy), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (10 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (11 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Defense, End Zone-Tight] (copy), 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (12 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Kicks], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)
- NC State vs. Virginia Tech (13 of 15) [labeled on cassette as Kicking Master], 18 Nov. 1989 (Carton 74)